  --.-- STARTERS 



BATTERED KAPENTA         K80
FRESH KAPENTA LIGHTLY DUSTED IN OUR HOUSE 
BATTER & DEEPED FRIED


FRIED OKRA               K60
CRISPY SALTY OKRA CHIPS. ONCE YOU START 
YOU WONT STOP


CHICKEN WINGS            K95

CHOOSE FROM BUFFALO /PERT PERI / STICKY 
SAUCE.


PERI PERI CHICKEN LIVERS K80

PERI PER! MARINATED CHICKEN LIVERS, FLAMING 
TO PERFECTION

SKEWERED CHICKEN GIBLETS K70
FLAMED GRILLED WIN BBQ SAUCE

